A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  - Appropriations - Alphabetical, 1919-1929; 2
    - Fellowship Applications, 1925-27 (Box 48, Folder 1094)
    - Fellowship Applications - Public Health, 1922-24 (Box 48, Folder 1095)
    - General Feng, 1927-28 (Box 48, Folder 1096)
    - (Folder does not esist.) (Box 48, Folder 1097)
    - Miss Feng, 1927 (Box 48, Folder 1098)
    - J. Y. Ferguson, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 1099)
    - Field Studies, 1925-28 (Box 48, Folder 1100)
      Kala-azar, sandflies, rodent lice, foot and mouth disease, rinderpest
    - Charles Fife, 1921-22 (Box 48, Folder 1101)
    - Fifth Avenue Hospital, 1924 (Box 48, Folder 1102)
    - Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church, 1921 (Box 48, Folder 1103)
    - First Provincial Middle School, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 1104)
    - Galen Fisher, 1920-27 (Box 48, Folder 1105)
    - Mrs. Harold Fisher, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 1106)
    - Alice Fitzgerald, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 1107)
    - Edward Forbes, 1922 (Box 48, Folder 1108)
    - D. E. Ford, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 1109)
    - Abraham Flexner, 1919-27 (Box 48, Folder 1110)
    - Foreign Christian Missionary Society, 1919-23 (Box 49, Folder 1111)
      See also United Christian Missionary Society
    - Foreign Christian Missionary Society - Luchowfu, 1919-23 (Box 49, Folder 1112)
    - Foreign Christian Missionary Society - Nantungchow, 1922-23 (Box 49, Folder 1113)
    - Foreign Missions Conference (Box 49, Folder 1114)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1926-28 (Box 49, Folder 1115)
    - Fordham University, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1116)
    - J. A. Fordyce, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1117)
    - Harry Emerson Fosdick, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 1118)
    - Raymond B. Fosdick, 1921-27 (Box 49, Folder 1119)
    - John H. Foster, 1919-24 (Box 49, Folder 1120)
    - Henry Fowler, 1922-23 (Box 49, Folder 1121)
    - Laurence K. Frank, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 1122)
    - Fu Chung College of Mines, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 1123)
    - Fuh Tan University, 1922-27 (Box 49, Folder 1124)
    - Frank Fulton, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1125)
    - Mrs. Brownell Gage, 1919-24 (Box 49, Folder 1126)
    - Mr. Bailey, 1923-24 (Box 49, Folder 1127)
    - Gasoline, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 1128)
    - Frederick T. Gates, 1919-22 (Box 49, Folder 1129)
    - N. Gist Gee, 1924-28 (Box 49, Folder 1130)
    - General Education Board, 1921-24 (Box 49, Folder 1131)
    - Geological Survey of China, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 1132)
    - German Influence in China, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 1133)
    - Robert Gesell, 1918-19 (Box 49, Folder 1134)
    - John M. Gibbs, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 1135)
    - Gingling College, 1919-25 (Box 49, Folder 1136)
    - Gingling College, 1919-25 (Box 49, Folder 1137)
    - Gingling College, 1919-25 (Box 49, Folder 1138)
    - Gingling College, 1919-25 (Box 49, Folder 1139)
    - Gingling College, 1926-28 (Box 50, Folder 1140)
    - E. S. Glines, 1924 (Box 50, Folder 1141)
    - Frank J. Goodnow, 1919-26 (Box 50, Folder 1142)
    - L. C. Goodrich, 1920-28 (Box 50, Folder 1143)
    - L. C. Goodrich, 1920-28 (Box 50, Folder 1144)
    - L. C. Goodrich, 1920-28 (Box 50, Folder 1145)
    - L. C. Goodrich, 1920-28 (Box 50, Folder 1146)
    - Mrs. L. C. Goodrich, 1924 (Box 50, Folder 1147)
    - G. Douglas Gray, 1923-24 (Box 50, Folder 1148)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 1149)
    - Jerome D. Greene, 1919-28 (Box 50, Folder 1150)
    - Kate Greene, 1925-27 (Box 50, Folder 1151)
    - Roger S. Greene, 1919-28 (Box 50, Folder 1152)
      Political situation, famine
    - Roger S. Greene, 1919-28 (Box 50, Folder 1153)
    - Theodore O. Greene, 1925-26 (Box 50, Folder 1154)
    - Grew Fund, 1922-23 (Box 50, Folder 1155)
    - Grinnell College, 1923-24 (Box 50, Folder 1156)
    - Benjamin Grodnitzky, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 1157)
    - F. Gudernatsch, 1927-28 (Box 50, Folder 1158)
    - William H. Gutelius, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 1159)
    - Hackett Medical School, 1919-23 (Box 51, Folder 1160)
    - George Hadden, 1924 (Box 51, Folder 1161)
    - M. E. Haggerty, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 1162)
    - Hall Trust Fund, 1925-26 (Box 51, Folder 1163)
    - U. S. Halstead, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 1164)
    - Julia Han, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 1165)
    - L. C. Han, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 1166)
    - Elizabeth Hand, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 1167)
    - Hangchow Hospital, 1919-27 (Box 51, Folder 1168)
      Local weekly newsletters; political situation and local events.
    - Hangchow Hospital, 1919-27 (Box 51, Folder 1169)
    - Hangchow Hospital, 1919-27 (Box 51, Folder 1170)
    - Hankow Health Bureau, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 1171)
    - Hankow Hospital Union, 1926 (Box 51, Folder 1172)
    - Harbin Medical Society, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 1173)
    - Harkness Fund, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 1174)
    - F. F. Carr Harris, 1926 (Box 51, Folder 1175)
    - Marguerite Harrison, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 1176)
    - Hartford Hospital, 1920-25 (Box 51, Folder 1177)
    - Harvard University, 1917-27 (Box 51, Folder 1178)
    - S. Hata, 1921-23 (Box 51, Folder 1179)
    - John D. Hayes, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 1180)
    - Maxim Hefftler, 1924-25 (Box 51, Folder 1181)
    - Victor G. Heiser, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 1182)
    - Ruth Hemenway, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 1183)
    - L. J. Henderson, 1919-20 (Box 51, Folder 1184)
    - Cullen Hendry, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 1185)
    - A. H. Hepburn, 1921-22 (Box 51, Folder 1186)
    - Marshall Hertig, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 1187)
    - M. L. Herzig, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 1188)
    - Higher Normal College, 1919-23 (Box 51, Folder 1189)
    - Frank Hinckley, 1926-27 (Box 51, Folder 1190)
    - W. G. Hiltner, 1923-26 (Box 51, Folder 1191)
    - B. C. Ho, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 1192)
    - C. J. Ho, 1924 (Box 51, Folder 1193)
    - T. E. Ho, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 1194)
    - T. K. Ho, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 1195)
    - William Ho, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 1196)
    - Alfred Hogg, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 1197)
    - James Hogg, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 1198)
    - Joanna Holbrook, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 1199)
    - Home Insurance Company, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 1200)
    - Hong Kong University, 1924 (Box 51, Folder 1201)
    - Hookworm, 1923-24 (Box 51, Folder 1202)
    - Hopei University, 1922-24 (Box 51, Folder 1203)
    - Hospital Bureau of Standards and Supplies, 1919-22 (Box 51, Folder 1204)
    - Burton Houseman, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 1205)
    - Hsa Ling Hsiung, 1923-27 (Box 51, Folder 1206)
    - Hsin Kai Lu Hospital, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 1207)
    - Hsiang Shan Children's Home, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 1208)
    - Hsing Ya Medical College, 1926-28 (Box 52, Folder 1209)
      Union College, see Shanghai Union Medical School. China provincial authority, student unrest, political situation.
    - Hsing Ya Medical College, 1926-28 (Box 52, Folder 1210)
    - Hsing Ya Medical College, 1926-28 (Box 52, Folder 1211)
    - Hsing Ya Medical College, 1926-28 (Box 52, Folder 1212)
    - Hsing Ya Medical College, 1926-28 (Box 52, Folder 1213)
    - Hsing Ya Medical College, 1926-28 (Box 52, Folder 1214)
    - E. T. Hsieh, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 1215)
    - C. K. Hsih, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 1216)
    - Han Chung Hsiu, 1920 (Box 52, Folder 1217)
    - C. H. Hu, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 1218)
    - Shih Hu, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 1219)
    - Tsefang Huang, 1921-24 (Box 52, Folder 1220)
    - Tsefang Huang, 1921-24 (Box 52, Folder 1221)
    - Tsefang Huang, 1921-24 (Box 52, Folder 1222)
    - Huchow Union Hospital, 1919-24 (Box 52, Folder 1223)
    - Huchow Union Hospital, 1919-24 (Box 52, Folder 1224)
    - Huchow Union Hospital, 1925-28 (Box 53, Folder 1225)
    - Huchow Union Hospital, 1925-28 (Box 53, Folder 1226)
    - Ellsworth Huntingdon, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 1227)
    - C. F. Huo, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 1228)
    - Hupei Provincial Medical School, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 1229)
    - Allen C. Hutcheson, 1921-23 (Box 53, Folder 1230)
    - Illiteracy, 1924-25 (Box 53, Folder 1231)
    - Immigration, 1924-28 (Box 53, Folder 1232)
    - Indemnity Fund, 1922-27 (Box 53, Folder 1233)
      Boxer Indemnity, China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, anti-opium campaign, education regulations.
    - Indemnity Fund, 1922-27 (Box 53, Folder 1234)
    - Index Medicus, 1922 (Box 53, Folder 1235)
    - India House, 1922 (Box 53, Folder 1236)
    - Infant's Hospital, 1922 (Box 53, Folder 1237)
    - M. Inoye, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 1238)
    - Insane Asylum-Chulan, 1927-28 (Box 53, Folder 1239)
    - Institute of Human Biology, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 1240)
    - Institute of International Education, 1921-26 (Box 53, Folder 1241)
    - Institute of International Relations, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 1242)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1926-28 (Box 53, Folder 1243)
    - Institute of Social & Religious Research, 1924-25 (Box 53, Folder 1244)
    - Institute of Technical Training, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 1245)
    - Insurance & Annuities, 1923-28 (Box 53, Folder 1246)
    - Interchurch World Movement, 1920 (Box 53, Folder 1247)
    - International Association of Agricultural Missions, 1920 (Box 53, Folder 1248)
    - International Banking Corporation, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 1249)
    - International Education Board, 1923-26 (Box 53, Folder 1250)
    - International Famine Relief Commission, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 1251)
    - International House, 1924-28 (Box 53, Folder 1252)
    - International Institute of Agriculture, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 1253)
    - International Institute of China, 1920-27 (Box 53, Folder 1254)
    - International Missionary Council, 1924-28 (Box 54, Folder 1255)
      Christian education, anti-Christian feeling, Chinese education, tropical hygiene, indemnity funds, opium, political situation.
    - International Missionary Council, 1924-28 (Box 54, Folder 1256)
    - Isolation Hospital, 1922 (Box 54, Folder 1257)
    - Japan, 1922-27 (Box 54, Folder 1258)
      Earthquake, emergency relief, nurses.
    - Japan, 1922-27 (Box 54, Folder 1259)
    - The Japanese-American, 1924 (Box 54, Folder 1260)
    - Japanese Christian Association, 1927 (Box 54, Folder 1261)
    - Japanese Consul, 1921 (Box 54, Folder 1262)
    - Japanese Legation, 1922-26 (Box 54, Folder 1263)
    - Japanese Medical Literature, 1919-20 (Box 54, Folder 1264)
      Abstracts
    - Japanese Society, 1921-23 (Box 54, Folder 1265)
    - Charles Jefferson, 1923 (Box 54, Folder 1266)
    - Jefferson Academy, 1923-24 (Box 54, Folder 1267)
    - Jefferson Medical College, 1920 (Box 54, Folder 1268)
    - Dr. Jennings, 1920 (Box 54, Folder 1269)
    - Lok Nin Jeu, 1923 (Box 54, Folder 1270)
    - John McCormick Institute for Infectious Diseases, 1919-22 (Box 54, Folder 1271)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1925-27 (Box 54, Folder 1272)
    - Johns Hopkins, 1919-27 (Box 54, Folder 1273)
    - Johns Hopkins, 1919-27 (Box 54, Folder 1274)
    - H. H. Johnson, 1923 (Box 54, Folder 1275)
    - John Johnson, 1922 (Box 54, Folder 1276)
    - Nelson Johnson, 1921 (Box 54, Folder 1277)
    - T. B. Johnson, 1922 (Box 54, Folder 1278)
    - E. M. Johnstone, 1922-27 (Box 54, Folder 1279)
    - Joint Committee of Women's Colleges in the Orient, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 1280)
    - Harry Pratt Judson, 1919-27 (Box 54, Folder 1281)
    - Ida Kahn, 1919 (Box 54, Folder 1282)
    - K. Kamo, 1922 (Box 54, Folder 1283)
    - Kiyoshi Kanai, 1923-27 (Box 54, Folder 1284)
    - Yu Hsin Kao, 1924 (Box 54, Folder 1285)
    - C. V. Kappers, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 1286)
    - Edward Kau, 1920-25 (Box 55, Folder 1287)
    - L. S. Kau, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1288)
    - Lim Bok Kau, 1927-28 (Box 55, Folder 1289)
    - Keijo University, 1926 (Box 55, Folder 1290)
    - Keio University, 1920-22 (Box 55, Folder 1291)
    - Vernon Kellog, 1922-24 (Box 55, Folder 1292)
    - R. R. Kendall, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 1293)
    - R. Brent Keyser, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1294)
    - Kiangsu Medical School, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 1295)
    - Kiangsu Provincial Medical College, 1922-26 (Box 55, Folder 1296)
    - Kiangsu University, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 1297)
    - Frank Kiernan, 1925 (Box 55, Folder 1298)
    - A. R. Kilgore, 1924 (Box 55, Folder 1299)
    - Thomas Killion, 1926 (Box 55, Folder 1300)
    - A. H. Kim, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 1301)
    - C. S. Kim, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1302)
    - Y. Kim, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1303)
    - Kuei Ju King, 1926-27 (Box 55, Folder 1304)
    - Kuei Ju King, 1926-27 (Box 55, Folder 1305)
    - Sohtsu G. King, 1926 (Box 55, Folder 1306)
    - W. V. King, 1923 (Box 55, Folder 1307)
    - King Edward VII Medical School, 1924 (Box 55, Folder 1308)
    - King's College, 1922 (Box 55, Folder 1309)
    - King's County Hospital, 1922-23 (Box 55, Folder 1310)
    - Edward Kirk, 1923 (Box 55, Folder 1311)
    - John Kirk, 1926-27 (Box 55, Folder 1312)
    - Robert H. Kirk, 1923-24 (Box 55, Folder 1313)
    - Kitsato Institute, 1923-25 (Box 55, Folder 1314)
    - George Kittridge, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1315)
    - Knapp Memorial Eye Hospital, 1921 (Box 55, Folder 1316)
    - C. A. Koford, 1919-22 (Box 55, Folder 1317)
    - Z. W. Koh, 1922-27 (Box 55, Folder 1318)
    - Hideyo Komuro, 1923-24 (Box 55, Folder 1319)
    - Wellington Koo, 1920-22 (Box 55, Folder 1320)
    - Korean Students, 1921 (Box 55, Folder 1321)
    - Kuling American School, 1926 (Box 55, Folder 1322)
    - Kuling Medical Missionary Association, 1922 (Box 55, Folder 1323)
    - Hsien - Wu Kung (Box 55, Folder 1324)
    - Kung Yee University Medical School, 1919-27 (Box 55, Folder 1325)
      Student agitation, political situation
    - Yas Kuno, 1924-25 (Box 55, Folder 1326)
    - Yung Kwai, 1922 (Box 55, Folder 1327)
    - Kwangchi Hospital, 1928 (Box 55, Folder 1328)
    - Paul Kwei, 1923 (Box 55, Folder 1329)
    - Miss Kwong, 1922 (Box 55, Folder 1330)
    - Kwong Wah Medical College, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 1331)
    - G. E. Kyle, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1332)
    - Lakeside Hospital, 1921-23 (Box 56, Folder 1333)
    - C. E. Lane, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 1334)
    - Lankenan Hospital, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 1335)
    - Sr. M. Laurentine, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 1336)
    - League of Red Cross, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 1337)
    - C. C. Lee, 1919-20 (Box 56, Folder 1338)
    - C. M. Lee, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 1339)
    - John Y. Lee, 1919-27 (Box 56, Folder 1340)
    - S. C. Lee, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 1341)
    - S. F. Lee, 1921 (Box 56, Folder 1342)
    - Ma Tsia Lee Biological Station, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 1343)
    - Lee Higginson & Co., 1922-27 (Box 56, Folder 1344)
    - Mr. Legndre, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 1345)
    - Lehigh University, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 1346)
    - H. S. Leiper, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 1347)
    - R. T. Leiper, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 1348)
    - Eliza Leonard, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 1349)
    - Leprosy (Box 56, Folder 1350)
    - C. B. Lesher, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 1351)
    - Stephen C. Lewis, 1925-27 (Box 56, Folder 1352)
    - Bi Cu Li, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 1353)
    - J. C. Li, 1925-26 (Box 56, Folder 1354)
    - K. C. Li, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 1355)
    - Kin Li, 1926-27 (Box 56, Folder 1356)
    - P. H. Li, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 1357)
    - Shih Tsun Li, 1918-20 (Box 56, Folder 1358)
    - T. Y. Li, 1926-27 (Box 56, Folder 1359)
    - Yuan Hung Li, 1922-27 (Box 56, Folder 1360)
    - Yutin C. Li, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 1361)
    - P. K. Liang, 1916-23 (Box 56, Folder 1362)
    - C. C. Liau, 1919-26 (Box 56, Folder 1363)
    - Library of the International Missionary Council, 1926 (Box 56, Folder 1364)
    - Lucy Lieo, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 1365)
    - Life Extension Institute, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 1366)
    - Likeh Ming Memorial, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 1367)
    - Lok Kiu Lim, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 1368)
    - L. Y. Lin, 1926 (Box 56, Folder 1369)
    - Tung Yee Lin, 1926 (Box 56, Folder 1370)
    - Grace C. H. Ling, 1920-21 (Box 56, Folder 1371)
    - S. Ling, 1926 (Box 56, Folder 1372)
    - Lingnan University, 1927-28 (Box 56, Folder 1373)
      See also Canton Christian College; political situation
    - Lingnan University, 1927-28 (Box 56, Folder 1374)
    - Lingnan University, 1927-28 (Box 56, Folder 1375)
    - J. C. Lipman, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 1376)
    - C. L. Liu, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 1377)
    - John R. W. Liu, 1920 (Box 56, Folder 1378)
    - E. C. Lobenstine, 1923-24 (Box 56, Folder 1379)
    - Lockhart Hall, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 1380)
    - Mrs. Oliver T. Logan, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 1381)
    - London Missionary Society, 1919-27 (Box 56, Folder 1382)
    - London Mission Hospital - Hankow, 1919-27 (Box 56, Folder 1383)
    - London Mission Hospital - Siaochang, 1919-28 (Box 56, Folder 1384)
    - London Mission Hospital - Tientsin, 1919-24 (Box 56, Folder 1385)
    - London Mission Hospital - Tsangchow, 1919-27 (Box 56, Folder 1386)
    - W. T. Longcope, 1920-21 (Box 57, Folder 1387)
    - Long Island College Hospital, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 1388)
    - Los Angeles County Hospital, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 1389)
    - Los Angeles Department of Health, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 1390)
    - Mrs. Q. V. Lovering, 1920 (Box 57, Folder 1391)
    - Robert Lovett, 1919-20 (Box 57, Folder 1392)
    - Loyola University, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 1393)
    - Ling Lu Marine Biological Laboratory, 1927-28 (Box 57, Folder 1394)
    - Hwei Ling Lu, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 1395)
    - Tse Ken Lu, 1927-28 (Box 57, Folder 1396)
    - S. C. Lui, 1919 (Box 57, Folder 1397)
    - K. C. Lum, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1398)
    - Lying-In Hospital, 1919-23 (Box 57, Folder 1399)
    - B. M. Lyon, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1400)
    - A. B. Macallum, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 1401)
    - F. B. Mallory, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1402)
    - Manchurian Medical College, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 1403)
    - T. D. Mansfield, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1404)
    - Manfield and Sons, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1405)
    - H. C. Mao, 1925-28 (Box 57, Folder 1406)
    - Isaac Marcosson, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 1407)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1920-28 (Box 57, Folder 1408)
    - Mary Thompson Hospital, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 1409)
    - Maryland Department of Health, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1410)
    - Mass Education Movement, 1927-28 (Box 57, Folder 1411)
    - Massachusetts Chraritable Eye and Ear Infirmary, 1919-22 (Box 57, Folder 1412)
    - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1923-24 (Box 57, Folder 1413)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1922-26 (Box 57, Folder 1414)
    - Massachusetts Tuberculosis League, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 1415)
    - Vincent Massey, 1919 (Box 57, Folder 1416)
    - Maternity Hospital, Peking, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 1417)
    - Mayo Clinic, 1920-23 (Box 57, Folder 1418)
      Arrangements for school for medical missionaries
    - William McCall, 1922-23 (Box 57, Folder 1419)
    - Robert McClure, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 1420)
    - Mabry McCoy, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 1421)
    - McGill University, 1921-28 (Box 57, Folder 1422)
    - W. C. McLaughlin, 1924-26 (Box 57, Folder 1423)
    - Jay McLean, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1424)
    - McLean Hospital, 1923-24 (Box 57, Folder 1425)
    - Mechanical Stokers, 1922-24 (Box 57, Folder 1426)
      Peking Union Medical College Buildings
    - Mechanical Stokers, 1922-24 (Box 57, Folder 1427)
    - Mechanical Stokers, 1922-24 (Box 57, Folder 1428)
    - Medical College of Virginia, 1920-28 (Box 57, Folder 1429)
    - Medical Education, 1921-23 (Box 57, Folder 1430)
    - Medical Education in India, 1920 (Box 57, Folder 1431)
    - Medical Practice, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 1432)
    - Medicine as a Life Work, 1923-27 (Box 57, Folder 1433)
      Contest
    - Y. L. Mei, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 1434)
    - Thomas Meloy, 1922-25 (Box 57, Folder 1435)
      Technical Education
    - Memorial Hospital, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 1436)
    - E. Merrow, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 1437)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North, 1919-28 (Box 58, Folder 1438)
      Christianity and religion
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North, 1919-28 (Box 58, Folder 1439)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North, 1919-28 (Box 58, Folder 1440)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North, 1919-28 (Box 58, Folder 1441)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Chinkiang, 1923-27 (Box 58, Folder 1442)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Eastern Asia, 1922-23 (Box 58, Folder 1443)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Foochow, 1921-27 (Box 58, Folder 1444)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Hingwa, 1921-23 (Box 58, Folder 1445)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Kuikiang, 1915-25 (Box 58, Folder 1446)
      Women's Foreign Missionary Society, Lillian Wu
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Kutien, 1921-22 (Box 58, Folder 1447)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Nanchang, 1921-28 (Box 58, Folder 1448)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Peking, 1919-27 (Box 58, Folder 1449)
      Dentistry School
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Peking, 1919-27 (Box 58, Folder 1450)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Peking, 1919-27 (Box 58, Folder 1451)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Taianfu, 1921-25 (Box 58, Folder 1452)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Wuhu, 1919-28 (Box 59, Folder 1453)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Wuhu, 1919-28 (Box 59, Folder 1454)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Wuhu, 1919-28 (Box 59, Folder 1455)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Wuhu, 1919-28 (Box 59, Folder 1456)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Wuhu, 1919-28 (Box 59, Folder 1457)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Wuhu, 1919-28 (Box 59, Folder 1458)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - North - Yenping, 1919-25 (Box 59, Folder 1459)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North - Fukien Christian University, 1920-27 (Box 59, Folder 1460)
      Union University, political situation, religion, student unrest
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North - Fukien Christian University, 1920-27 (Box 59, Folder 1461)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North - Fukien Christian University, 1920-27 (Box 59, Folder 1462)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North - Fukien Christian University, 1920-27 (Box 59, Folder 1463)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North - Fukien Christian University, 1928 (Box 60, Folder 1464)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - North - Tongshan Anglo-Chinese College, 1920 (Box 60, Folder 1465)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - Women's Foreign Missionary Society, 1924-27 (Box 60, Folder 1466)
    - Methodist Episcopal Women's Hospital - Sleeper Davis, 1917-27 (Box 60, Folder 1467)
    - Methodist Episcopal Women's Hospital - Sleeper Davis, 1917-27 (Box 60, Folder 1468)
    - Methodist Episcopal Women's Hospital - Tientsin, 1919-25 (Box 60, Folder 1469)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - South, 1919-28 (Box 60, Folder 1470)
      X-ray, transmission of funds, real estate
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - South - Changchow, 1921-25 (Box 60, Folder 1471)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - South - Soochow, 1919-26 (Box 60, Folder 1472)
      Political situation, tapeworm, X-ray, buildings, hookworm
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - South - Soochow, 1919-26 (Box 60, Folder 1473)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - South - Soochow, 1919-26 (Box 60, Folder 1474)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - South - Soochow, 1919-26 (Box 60, Folder 1475)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - South - Soochow, 1919-26 (Box 60, Folder 1476)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - South - Soochow, 1927-28 (Box 61, Folder 1477)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - South - Soochow University, 1922-28 (Box 61, Folder 1478)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - South - Soochow University, 1922-28 (Box 61, Folder 1479)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - South - Soochow University, 1922-28 (Box 61, Folder 1480)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - South - Soochow University, 1922-28 (Box 61, Folder 1481)